question_data = {"response_code": 0,
                 "results": [
                     {"category": "General Knowledge", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
                      "question": "&quot;Typewriter&quot; is the longest word that can be typed using only the first row on a QWERTY keyboard.",
                      "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
                     {"category": "General Knowledge", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
                      "question": "Coca-Cola&#039;s original colour was green.", "correct_answer": "False",
                      "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"category": "General Knowledge", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
                                                       "question": "Furby was released in 1998.", "correct_answer": "True",
                                                       "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
                     {"category": "General Knowledge", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
                      "question": "An eggplant is a vegetable.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
                     {"category": "General Knowledge", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
                      "question": "Fast food restaurant chains Carl&#039;s Jr. and Hardee&#039;s are owned by the same company.",
                      "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
                     {"category": "General Knowledge", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
                      "question": "The scientific name for the Southern Lights is Aurora Australis?", "correct_answer": "True",
                      "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"category": "General Knowledge", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
                                                        "question": "Haggis is traditionally ate on Burns Night.",
                                                        "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
                     {"category": "General Knowledge", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
                      "question": "Popcorn was invented in 1871 by Frederick W. Rueckheim in the USA where he sold the snack on the streets of Chicago.",
                      "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
                     {"category": "General Knowledge", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
                      "question": "The commercial UK channel ITV stands for &quot;International Television&quot;.",
                      "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
                     {"category": "General Knowledge", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
                      "question": "The pickled gherkin was first added to hamburgers because a US health law required all fast-food to include a source of Vitamin C.",
                      "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}]}
